ADIYANSAH S.KOM

Tambun Selatan, Bekasi Phone: +6287741413213

Email: adiyansahcode@gmail.com Web: www.adiyansahcode.id



About Me

I am a Developer. I have become a web developer since 2014. At the beginning of my career i use Codeigniter in my project, then I use the PHP Phalcon as a backend, Laravel, Lumen and I also used the Java Spring in my project. and now i focus as backend developer who understands the Restful API. I can also analyze a problem and then make into a database design and system design.

Skill & Expertise

PHP Developer:

JavaScript Developer:

Backend Developer:

Database Analyst:

System Analyst:

Data Analyst:

Work Experience

Web Developer on PT. Prima Tangguh Abadi

October 2015 – March 2016

Analyze and creating a ERP system with Codeigniter and SQL Server.

Web Developer on PT. Loka Citra Media

April 2016 – July 2018

Analyze and creating a Web-Base system with Codeigniter and MySQL.

Backend Developer on PT. Sigma Cipta Caraka

August 2018 – present

Analyze and creating RESTful Web Services with Phalcon and Java Spring.

Education

AMIK BINA SARANA INFORMATIKA, BEKASI

Manajemen Informatika D₃

2011 - 2014

STMIK NUSA MANDIRI, JAKARTA

Sistem Informasi S1

2014 - 2015

PORTOFOLIO

1. Project Link2bos.com

Owner : PT. BAE Orbit Senusantara

Industry : MLM System

Role : WEB Developer (PHP Codeigniter)

Year : 2018

2. Project IbosAcademy.com

Owner : PT. BAE Orbit Senusantara

Industry : MLM System

Role : WEB Developer (PHP Codeigniter)

Year : 2018

3. Project Hirest

Owner : TelkomSigma

Industry : Information and Telecommunication Role : Backend Developer (PHP Phalcon)

Year : 2018

4. Project MBike

Owner : TelkomSigma

Industry : Information and Telecommunication Role : Backend Developer (Java Spring)

Year : 2019

5. Project NSAM Enhancement and BroFist

Owner : Telkomsel Industry : Analytic Tools

Role : Backend Developer (PHP Phalcon)

Year : 2019

6. Project NRA

Owner : Telkomsel Industry : Analytic Tools

Role : Data Analysis (Power BI)

Year : 2020

7. Project Etlha

Owner : Bank DKI

Industry : Information and Telecommunication

Role : WEB Developer (Laravel)

Year : 2020















8. Project Iriis

Owner Industry Role : Telkomsel

: Analytic Tools : Backend Developer (PHP Phalcon)

Year : 2020

